Guide to the John Hollander Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- January 2008 Acquisition, 1949-2006; 18.09; (22 boxes)
  - Writings, 1951-2006; Series II
    - Writings of John Hollander
      - "In Time and Place", 1975-1987; 6 (Box 16)
      - "Rhyme's Reason, 1989; 4 (Box 16)
      - "Translations MSS", undated (Box 16)
      - 'Other' books, 1962-2003 (Box 16)
      - "Musical Entertainments", 1961-1976; 3 (Box 16)
      - "Musical Entertainments", 1961-1976; 2 (Box 17)
      - "Prose Fiction", 1975-1979; 3 (Box 17)
      - "From the desktop", 1977-2003; 3 (Box 17)
      - Unpublished, 1954-1999; 2 (Box 17)
      - Various manuscripts, 1968-2004; 7 (Box 17)
      - "Dal Vero - Extra Material", 1964-1983; 2 (Box 17)
      - "Originality", undated (Box 17)
      - Printed articles, 1957-1996 (Box 17)
      - Various manuscripts, 1972-1993; 3 (Box 18)
      - "William Bailey Book", 1990 (Box 18)
  - Other Material, Series III
    - Teaching Files
      - Children's Literature, 1960-1977; 3 (Box 18)
      - Milton, 1973-1985; 3 (Box 18)
      - Poetic Translation, undated (Box 18)
      - Poetics, 1981-1990; 3 (Box 18)
      - Science and Poetry, undated; 5 (Box 18)
      - 17th Century Graduate Course, undated (Box 18)
    - Music Files
      - "The Death of Moses", 1989-1992; 2 (Box 18)
      - Programs, 1956-2002; 2 (Box 18)
      - Clippings, 1964-1975 (Box 18)
      - Scores, 1959-1999; 7 (Box 18)
    - Printed material, 1949-2006; 2 (Box 19)
    - New York Public Library Literary Lion Award, undated (Box 20)
  - Oversize
    - "Spectral Emanations" proof, 1978 (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - "Tales Told of the Fathers" proof, 1975 (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - "Picture Window" jacket proof, undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - "Pantun" score, undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Restricted Fragile
    Computer disk: Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Compact disk, 2006 February 7 (Box 22)
      "From Suzie Forster"